cpu-world.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy

##  Personal information collected on CPU-World.com

  * We use cookies to store username and logged-in status of all users registered in the forum. For these users we also collect e-mail address and other information provided by users during registration.
  * We log search text submitted into site search, S-spec search, CPU search and CPU identification tools.
  * From time to time we may embed analytics script into our web pages. This script collects basic information about your visit and your browser, and reports them back to the server. When provided on the page, the script uses cookies to prevent sending certain information more than once.
  * For each web page request our server automatically logs date and time of the request, visitor's IP address, accessed URL, and browser type.
  * Many CPU-World pages display advertisements supplied by Google via their Adsense program. Google tracks all clicks on Adsense ads, and they may also track visited pages for each site visitor. To serve targeted ads, based in prior visits to this and other websites, Google stores cookies in your browser when you view or click an ad. You can opt-out of this cookie on [this page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). Please consult Google privacy policy for more information.

##  How personal information is used

  * Personal information and cookies are used to allow registered users to access the forum. Some information about registered users, such as first and last name, is displayed in the forum members list.
  * We can use registered user's e-mail address to contact him/her in cases if there is a problem with user's account.
  * Information about all visited pages is used to track abusive visitors and automated bots, such as spam bots, crawlers, etc. This information is also used to generate site usage reports. The server logs are stored on temporary basis and deleted after several months.
  * Logged search text and identification text are used to improve the quality of search and identification tools. This information may be also utilized to track abusive visitors, such as visitors trying to post spam or break into the site.
  * We do not share any log files and personal information of our users with third parties.

If you have any question about privacy policy please contact us.
